articlez.com 2016-10-18

# Articlez.com Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to everyone at Articlez.com. We are very serious about protecting any and all information you share with us.

### Customer and Member Information:

Any information provided to us, such as your name and email address, address, phone number, required tax documents etc, is held in strict confidence and will not be sold, exchanged, transmitted or rented to third parties. This information will only be used by Articlez.com for providing the services we offer as described throughout this website.

### Credit Card and Banking Information:

_Articlez.com does not directly process payments, and therefore neither collects not has access to, any financial information you provide through our online ordering system to procure any of our services._

We do maintain a record of your Paypal account email address but have no access to your personal information contained within that account.

### Email:

We require that you confirm your request to receive email from Articlez.com.

You may unsubscribe from any email correspondence from Articlez.com at any time by simply clicking the link provided at the bottom of all correspondence.

Articlez.com uses cookies for data tracking purposes. 

Some or all of the following data may be tracked using cookies:

  * Your IP address, browser platform
  * Access dates & times
  * The operating system you are using
  * The country in which you reside
  * Data of a statistical nature (that enables us to provide you with data such as page views and clicks originating from your account)

### Third Party Advertising:

Use of cookies and web beacons by third parties in the advertising process:

Advertising that is delivered or distributed by third party vendors on this site may make use of cookies or web beacons.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. You may go to http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html to opt out.

_Articlez.com makes no claims regarding the privacy policies of any third party site that is referenced via advertising or by a link provided by a customer in content submitted by that customer._

_Articlez.com makes no claim as to the accuracy of information provided by third party contributors to this website._

### Surveys:

From time to time Articlez.com may ask you to participate in surveys. Any information you provide via these surveys is totally optional, and 100% anonymous and is only used to gather data relating to providing better services to our customers.

### Legal:

_There may be rare occasions when we are required by law to disclose personal information to comply with a legal action that may have been served on our business operations._

Articlez.com may choose to amend this policy from time to time. if significant changes to our privacy policy occur, we will notify those who have agreed to receive corresponded from us.

 Loading...
